{
    "quizId" : "111111",
    "quizTitle" : "MyQuiz",
    "quizDomain" : {
        "domainId":120,
        "domain" : "MySQL"
},
    "quizDuration" : "1",
    "questions" : [     
 {
            "questionId" : "841",
            "question" : "An ________ is a set of entities of the same type that share the same properties, or attributes",
            "difficulty" : "MED",
            "correctOption" : "Entity set",
            "domain" : {
                           "domainId":120,
                           "domain" : "MySQL"
            },
            "option1" : "Entity set",
            "option2" : "Attribute set",
            "option3" : "Relation set",
            "option4" : "Entry set"
        },

        {
            "questionId" : "842",
            "question" : "How should a many-to-many relationship be handled?",
            "difficulty" : "MED",
            "correctOption" : "By adding a join table",
           "domain" : {
                           "domainId":120,
                           "domain" : "MySQL"
            },
            "option1" : "By adding a join table",
            "option2" : "By adding an intersection table",
            "option3" : "By adding union table",
            "option4" : "By adding cartesian table"
        },

        {
            "questionId" : "843",
            "question" : " Which of the following is not true about SQL statements?",
            "difficulty" : "MED",
            "correctOption" : "Clauses must be written on separate lines",
              "domain" : {
                           "domainId":120,
                           "domain" : "MySQL"
            },
            "option1" : "SQL statements are not case sensitive",
            "option2" : "SQL statements can be written on one or more lines",
            "option3" : "Keywords cannot be split across lines",
            "option4" : "Clauses must be written on separate lines"
        },

        {
            "questionId" : "844",
            "question" : " What is returned by INSTR(‘TUTORIALS POINT’, ‘P’)?",
            "difficulty" : "MED",
            "correctOption" : "11",
              "domain" : {
                           "domainId":120,
                           "domain" : "MySQL"
            },
            "option1" : "11",
            "option2" : "10",
            "option3" : "POINT",
            "option4" : "TUTORIALS"
        },

         {
            "questionId" : "845",
            "question" : " What is returned by TRUNC(789.8389, 2)?",
            "difficulty" : "MED",
            "correctOption" : "789.83",
          "domain" : {
                           "domainId":120,
                           "domain" : "MySQL"
            },
            "option1" : "789.84",
            "option2" : "789.83",
            "option3" : "78",
            "option4" : "789.00"
        },
        
          {
            "questionId" : "846",
            "question" : " Which of the following is true about Cartesian Products?",
            "difficulty" : "MED",
            "correctOption" : "A Cartesian product is formed when a join condition is omitted",
              "domain" : {
                           "domainId":120,
                           "domain" : "MySQL"
            },
            "option1" : "A Cartesian product is formed when a join condition is omitted",
            "option2" : "A Cartesian product is formed when a join condition is valid",
            "option3" : "Some rows in the first table are joined to all rows in the second table",
            "option4" : "All rows in the first table are joined to some rows in the second table"
        },
    
    

        {
            "questionId" : "848",
            "question" : "Which data manipulation command is used to combines the records from one or more tables? ",
           "difficulty" : "MED",
            "correctOption" : "JOIN",
             "domain" : {
                           "domainId":120,
                           "domain" : "MySQL"
            },
            "option1" : "SELECT",
            "option2" : "JOIN",
            "option3" : "PROJECT",
            "option4" : "PRODUCT"
        },
    
        {
            "questionId" : "849",
            "question" : "Which operator is used to compare a value to a specified list of values? ",
           "difficulty" : "MED",
            "correctOption" : "IN",
              "domain" : {
                           "domainId":120,
                           "domain" : "MySQL"
            },
            "option1" : "BETWEEN",
            "option2" : "ANY",
            "option3" : "IN",
            "option4" : "ALL"
        },

        {
            "questionId" : "850",
            "question" : "The SQL used by front-end application programs to request data from the DBMS is called _______? ",
           "difficulty" : "MED",
            "correctOption" : "DML",
              "domain" : {
                           "domainId":120,
                           "domain" : "MySQL"
            },
            "option1" : "DML",
            "option2" : "DDL",
            "option3" : "VDL",
            "option4" : "SDL"
        },
            
        {

        "questionId" : "851",
            "question" : "Which of the following is a comparison operator in SQL?",
           "difficulty" : "MED",
            "correctOption" : "Double equal sign ( == )",
            "domain" : {
                           "domainId":120,
                           "domain" : "MySQL"
            },
            "option1" : "Double equal sign ( == )",
            "option2" : "LIKE",
            "option3" : "BETWEEN",
            "option4" : "Single equal sign ( = )"
       
         },


        {

        "questionId" : "853",
            "question" : "Which data type can store unstructured data in a column? ",
           "difficulty" : "MED",
            "correctOption" : "RAW",
            "domain" : {
                           "domainId":120,
                           "domain" : "MySQL"
            },
            "option1" : "RAW",
            "option2" : "CHAR",
            "option3" : "NUMERIC",
            "option4" : "VARCHAR"
       
         },
   
        {

             "questionId" : "854",
            "question" : "The virtual table that its created by data from the result of an SQL 'Select' statement is called __? ",
            "difficulty" : "MED",
            "correctOption" : "view",
            "domain" : {
                           "domainId":120,
                           "domain" : "MySQL"
            },
            "option1" : "view",
            "option2" : "synonym",
            "option3" : "sequence",
            "option4" : "transaction"
       
         },


          {

            "questionId" : "855",
            "question" : "To delete a database ____ command is uesd ",
           "difficulty" : "MED",
            "correctOption" : "drop database database_name",
            "domain" : {
                           "domainId":120,
                           "domain" : "MySQL"
            },
            "option1" : "Delete database database_name",
            "option2" : "Delete database_name",
            "option3" : "drop database database_name",
            "option4" : "drop databse_name"
       
         },


        {

            "questionId" : "856",
            "question" : "Which of the following procedures are created by user for own actions? ",
           "difficulty" : "MED",
            "correctOption" : "user defined stored procedure",
             "domain" : {
                           "domainId":120,
                           "domain" : "MySQL"
            },
            "option1" : "Extented procedure",
            "option2" : "user defined stored procedure",
            "option3" : "CLR stored procedure",
            "option4" : "All of the above"
       
         },

          {

            "questionId" : "857",
            "question" : "system defined procedure logically appear in? ",
           "difficulty" : "MED",
            "correctOption" : "sys schema",
            "domain" : {
                           "domainId":120,
                           "domain" : "MySQL"
            },
            "option1" : "sys schema",
            "option2" : "stor schema",
            "option3" : "proc schema",
            "option4" : "All of the above"
       
         },

          {
           "questionId" : "858",
            "question" : "The ----- operator is usedfor patten matching",
            "difficulty" : "MED",
            "correctOption" : "LIKE",
            "domain" : {
                           "domainId":120,
                           "domain" : "MySQL"
            },
            "option1" : " DISTINCT ",
            "option2" : "LIKE",
            "option3" : "GROUP BY ",
            "option4" : "ORDER BY"
        },

         {
           "questionId" : "859",
            "question" : "which of the following is not a relational database",
            "difficulty" : "MED",
            "correctOption" : "Reflex",
             "domain" : {
                           "domainId":120,
                           "domain" : "MySQL"
            },
            "option1" : " dBASE",
            "option2" : "4th Dimension",
            "option3" : "foxPro ",
            "option4" : "Reflex"
        },
        
        {
           "questionId" : "860",
            "question" : " A level that describes data stored in a database and the relationships among the data",
            "difficulty" : "MED",
            "correctOption" :"logical",
             "domain" : {
                           "domainId":120,
                           "domain" : "MySQL"
            },
            "option1" : " physical",
            "option2" : "logical",
            "option3" : "user ",
            "option4" : "view"
        },
        {
        "questionId" : "861",
            "question" : " What is a view?",
            "difficulty" : "MED",
            "correctOption" :"A view is a virtual table which results of executing a pre-compiled query",
             "domain" : {
                           "domainId":120,
                           "domain" : "MySQL"
            },
            "option1" : "A view is a special stored procedure executed when certain event occurs",
            "option2" : "A view is a virtual table which results of executing a pre-compiled query",
            "option3" : "A view is a database diagram",
            "option4" : "None of the Mentioned"
        },
        {
        "questionId" : "862",
            "question" : " Dynamic Management View is a type of ___________",
            "difficulty" : "MED",
            "correctOption" :"System Defined Views",
             "domain" : {
                           "domainId":120,
                           "domain" : "MySQL"
            },
            "option1" : "System Defined Views",
            "option2" : "User Defined View",
            "option3" : "Simple View",
            "option4" : "Complex View"
        },      

        {

            "questionId" : "863",
            "question" : "  ___________ is stored only in the Master database",
            "difficulty" : "MED",
            "correctOption" :"None of the mentioned",
            "domain" : {
                           "domainId":120,
                           "domain" : "MySQL"
            },
            "option1" : " Database-scoped Dynamic Management View",
            "option2" : "Complex View",
            "option3" : "Catalog View",
            "option4" : "None of the mentioned"
        },      
  
        {

            "questionId" : "864",
            "question" : "  Which of the following is not a NoSQL database?",
            "difficulty" : "MED",
            "correctOption" :"SQL server",
           "domain" : {
                           "domainId":120,
                           "domain" : "MySQL"
            },
            "option1" : "SQL server",
            "option2" : "MongoDB",
            "option3" : "Cassandra",
            "option4" : "None of the mentioned"
        },      

        
        {

            "questionId" : "865",
            "question" : "Which of the following are the simplest NoSQL databases?",
            "difficulty" : "MED",
            "correctOption" :"key-value",
            "domain" : {
                           "domainId":120,
                           "domain" : "MySQL"
            },
            "option1" : "key-value",
            "option2" : "wide-column",
            "option3" : "Document",
            "option4" : "All of the mentioned"
        },   
     
       {

            "questionId" : "867",
            "question" : " Transaction processing is associated with everything below except",
            "difficulty" : "MED",
            "correctOption" :"Conforming an action or triggering a response",
            "domain" : {
                           "domainId":120,
                           "domain" : "MySQL"
            },
            "option1" : "Conforming an action or triggering a response",
            "option2" : "Producing detail summary or exception report",
            "option3" : "Recording a business activity",
            "option4" : "Maintaining a data"
        },      

        {

            "questionId" : "868",
            "question" : "Point out the correct statement?",
            "difficulty" : "MED",
            "correctOption" :"All of the mentioned",
           "domain" : {
                           "domainId":120,
                           "domain" : "MySQL"
            },
            "option1" : "A Cursor is opened and populated by executing the SQL statement defined by the cursor",
            "option2" : "After data manipulation, we should close the cursor explicitly",
            "option3" : "A cursor is declared by defining the SQL statement that returns a result set",
            "option4" : "All of the mentioned"
        },     
      
       {

            "questionId" : "869",
            "question" : "Aggregate functions are functions that take a ___________ as input and return a single value?",
            "difficulty" : "MED",
            "correctOption" :"Collection of values",
             "domain" : {
                           "domainId":120,
                           "domain" : "MySQL"
            },
            "option1" : "Collection of values",
            "option2" : "Single value",
            "option3" : "Aggregate value",
            "option4" : "Both Collection of values & Single value"
        }
    
     
   ]
}














